You're right.
Kitagawa.
You look so beautiful today.
Um, are you sure you want to do it? I honestly don't mind.
Oh, Totes, I'm the one who's sweating it, not you. Trust me, it's all good.
If you say so. But let's wash it now. If we let it sit for too long, the sweat salt can ruin the style.
Mm-hmm.
Pour fabric softener into cold or warm water. After it's combed through, gently press the wig to wash it.
Does this look right?
Yep.
Oh, but it says not to rub or squeeze too hard. You can damage the wig.
Next up, change the water and keep pressing. Then towel wrap to absorb moisture. And lastly, place it outside to air dry.
Oh, sweet. That's not hard at all. I was thinking it.
Be sure to hand wash the outfit, too. It can develop sweat stains.
Cool.
Oh, apparently washing your wig too often is bad for it.
Huh?
Are you kidding me? That's what caused you to fall over?
You say that like smuggling ladies' undies is normal.
They were just stockings, right? Those are more along the lines of socks than underwear. Plus, it's pretty natural at that age.
If anything, I'm surprised you didn't find more of a variety.
That's not helpful at all.
Hi, I'm home.
Oh, hey, Grandpa. How's it going?
Sorry you had to man the shop alone for two weeks.
Hi there! Welcome home!
Welcome home!
Wakana!
Well, I'm relieved that that's all it was.
I'm sorry about that. I hope I didn't embarrass you back there.
Nah, I don't get embarrassed that easily.
So I see. I just figured...
We didn't do anything inappropriate.
Huh?
I know. It was pretty obvious when I saw that.
Still, weirdness aside, this is fine work. You made it?
Yeah, but it's still a work in progress.
Oh, really? You think so? Looks great to me.
I don't know. You see the spot over here? My stitches are so bad, I was about to pull out the glue gun.
Okay, I see it now. Well, it certainly is a different beast than Hina dolls.
Yeah. There are so many curved lines.
What's happening?
You see? It's almost impossible to get the right shape.
Oh, and then there's all this.
Oh, shit.
It can't be easy when you're used to cutting straight lines.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, shit! This 1000% cannot be true!
Am I really falling for Gojo right now?
What? No. No freaking way. How?
I like him, but do I like him? Do I love him?
Ew, no, shut up!
There's no way I'm in love with the dude who's besties with Grandpa!
That doesn't work for me!
Oh, look at him just standing around being adorable! I love him!
I can't do this! It's too exhausting! I've got a life to live!
I can't be obsessed with the cute little seamstress boy!
We've got food. Are you hungry?
What? No! Kill me, kill me, kill me!
Why don't you stay for dinner with us tonight?
Huh?
Yeah, you're already here. Make yourself at home.
This looks so good!
Gojo, shut up! You're a good cook, too? You're wrong!
It's not a big deal. I just learned how to cook because my parents are gone. Gotta eat something.
Oh, so you're like me, then?
Uh-huh.
Oh.
Okay, kinda. My mom got sick and passed a while ago, so then it was just me and my dad.
But when I got into high school, he had to transfer for his job.
With him away for work all the time, I pretty much live on my own.
Um, I'm obsessed with this Kabocha squash!
Oh, that's gotta be hard. Are you getting all your meals in?
Yep! The convenience store is where it's at!
Ugh!
But I do cook for myself when I can.
Check it! Natto fried rice.
I got fancy with the fried chicken and wieners.
It was so good, I ate some every day for a while.
I can't sew, but I can cook and do house stuff.
And you're sure you're okay? You get enough nutrition from that stuff?
Totally! I also drink milk and eat yogurt every day.
Does my body good!
Uh...
Maureen, why don't you start coming over for dinner from now on?
Huh?
You mind, Wakuna?
Of course not! What do you think, Kitagawa?
For real? Is it my birthday?
Oh, score!
Thanks!
So chivalrous of you to walk me to the station.
Thanks, but it's the least I can do for keeping you out so late.
Oh, whatever. Dinner was totes amazing,
and I had so much fun talking to your grandpa.
Hey, Gojo!
Yeah? What's up?
Uh...
So, um...
I'll see you tomorrow, right?
Sure.
See ya!
What the...
Why am I like this?
I didn't say anything awkward.
Awkward.
Why do I feel like I ruined everything?
We didn't do anything inappropriate.
Huh?
Nothing inappropriate.
Huh.
Uh...
Would it be so bad if we did?
And...
What if I actually said that?
Oh, for crying out loud.
Of course, it's gotta rain when I wanna get out.
Huh?
What's a little girl like her doing here all by herself?
Another friend of Wonkaness?
Pardon me.
You okay?
I'm sorry.
Okay?
You're okay.
I need you.
I know.
Yeah?
There's a little girl.
I can see.
I'm sorry.
I'll see you next time.
I'm home.
Oh, hello. Welcome back. I'm gonna head out.
Okay.
And you've got a friend waiting for you inside.
Soaked down to the bone.
So I let her use our bath.
Be a good host.
Make sure you've got a drink ready at least.
Huh?
That's weird.
Who could Grandpa have let into the house?
I'm pretty certain Kitagawa said she had work today.
And it's not like I have any other friends besides her.
Oh, no!
What if it's a con artist?
Or someone trying to rob the store?
Did they trick him somehow?
A kid?
What?
Hey, Grandpa?
Hmm?
How come this Hina doll doesn't have any hair on her head?
Well, that's the process.
We do their face and hair separately.
First, we draw the face.
Then we apply the hair.
Oh, wow!
I get it.
That's why she's so silky smooth.
Silky smooth.
I'm so sorry again.
So, um, did you want to see something in the shop?
Yes, sort of.
I want to see the outfits you made.
Oh, that's it!
She's in Dahina dolls and wants to learn how they're made.
How cool!
She came here by herself, so I bet that's why Grandpa assumed we were friends.
Y-yes, of course!
Just give me one moment, please.
Here we go.
All I need is your name and your school's name.
I'm Sajuna Inui.
I'm a second year at Sakura no Miya High.
What?
She's older than me.
What's wrong?
Nothing!
Nothing at all!
Who are you?
My name is Wakana Gojo.
I'm a first year in high school.
So, um, if you really want to see the outfits, I can show you now.
Just some, though.
Wait!
You can?
Like, right this second?
Sure.
Here they are.
Huh?
You're welcome to look as long as you like.
What an amazing feeling!
It really lifts me up to meet others who love Hina dolls the way I do.
Oh?
Are those dolls broken?
They don't have heads!
Sure they do.
Look over there.
Ugh!
They're crafted separately.
And then we combine them later.
Because that's not creepy or anything.
Oh, whoa.
But this kimono has Swarovski crystals.
And that one has lace!
Okay, I guess these dolls are kind of cool.
Thanks.
We've got all kinds.
Both traditional ones and modern ones.
Can I look at them up close?
Of course.
Oh!
Oh, don't worry.
I won't touch them.
I'm sure they're valuable.
I appreciate you being so considerate.
Wow.
These ones are extra pretty.
They might be my favorites.
Hey, good eye!
Those are some of the most popular ones we have.
Yeah, I bet.
Look how striking they are.
So cool.
Aren't they, though?
I love them, too.
Oh, you have to check out these ones over...
Is there any particular reason we're looking at dolls?
I guess because this is a Hina doll shop and dolls are what we sell?
I know that's what you sell!
I was asking you about your cosplay outfits!
Like this!
You made it, didn't you?
I came to order a cosplay, not some random doll!
Wait, what do you mean you want to order one?
Um...
I'm sorry.
I don't actually make those outfits professionally.
You saw it, didn't you?
Huh?
Earlier in the bathroom, when you marched in, you saw my...
That's voyeurism.
And you're a peeping dumb!
That's illegal!
And if I report you, you're gonna get arrested!
Arrested?
What?
No one else has ever seen me like that before.
Only you.
And if you don't want the police to find out, then I suggest you get to work.
You're making outfits for Juju now!
Huh?
Juju?
Her name is Juju.
Isn't she offensively cute?
I'm basically obsessed with her.
I know that name.
She's the cosplayer that Kitagawa said she liked.
But is that really her?
Huh?
Uh?
Oh!
Wow.
She looks really young, though.
How old do you think she is?
Hmm.
She might be in middle school.
Or at the end of grade school.
Please forgive my ignorance.
About what?
So, tell me, Juju.
What brings you here?
And how did you find out where I lived?
Well, I, uh...
I saw that marine girl's cosplay photo going around online, and...
Huh?
Who the heck's this?
She tweeted that she was going to a cosplay event after that.
So I went because I wanted to see her outfit up close.
And then...
And I feel like I'm about to burst!
Yeah, you probably are!
That outfit was measured in sewn to fit you perfectly!
When I found out you were the one who made it,
they went to a little stalker sauce and followed you home.
I'm sorry.
These cosplayers are nuts!
For real?
This is Sajuna Inui.
Bro, don't go telling her my real name!
I use a cosplay name for a reason!
My Juju's name is Sajuna?
You're why I'm that cute!
My name is Marin Kitagawa, and I'm obsessed with everything you do!
I love you so much!
I'm your biggest fan!
Too close!
Gee, you're just as gorgeous in person as you are in your photos!
You're so cute!
And look at your skin!
Who does your hair?
Wait, is Juju short for Sajuna?
Look, I didn't pick the name, it's just...
Actually, Inui told me she saw your cosplay photos, Kitagawa.
That's why she's here.
This cosplay goddess saw my pics?
She looked at me!
You have no idea how excited it makes me, Juju!
Holy crap, you really know I exist!
It probably popped up because you follow me online!
Now get out of my personal space!
I can't handle this like at all!
Neither can I, you're too close!
I'm not here for you, moron!
I'm trying to get hooked up with one of Wakana Gojo's custom outfits, so move!
Oh my god, you have like the prettiest eyes!
What's wrong with you?
So what do you think?
Are you in?
I need you to make Shionikaido's black lily outfit for me!
What? Shionton?
Wait, that girl you showed me?
The one with the blue dress?
Yep!
Shionton from Flower Princess Blaze!
It's popular with young girls, you've seen it?
I don't watch much anime.
Princess Lily!
Like she said, Shionikaido is a character who appears in the shoujo anime Flower Princess Blaze.
She and the protagonist Mirai decide to fight together by becoming the Flower Princess Magical Girl.
And that's the end of you!
Never again will you stand before the proud lily!
Magical girl!
Princess Lily!
But then...
No! It can't be true!
This whole time I've been fighting my sister?
She finds out that her older sister Neon is actually the enemy.
But how could you?
We're sisters!
This flower is totally opening up to you!
Xion!
Xion, we know the truth is cruel.
And the truth is happiness doesn't last forever.
Our false family.
The people who always look down on us.
Is it truly who you fought for?
Who you wanted to protect?
No!
Please stop!
What I wanted was destruction.
I want to destroy you all.
Please!
No!
Uh-oh!
Here comes Black Lily!
We've got trouble!
Tell the truth.
You wanted to ruin everything, didn't you?
You wanted a world that matched the hue of your heart.
As dark as the abyss.
Oh my god, the drama!
Neon was originally created as an enemy after her flower jewel was tainted from the shock of a broken heart.
It's so unbelievably tragic.
Because she does know her stuff.
I thought she was the type that fanned over what's popular without researching anything about the original work and just cosplay characters because their outfits were cute.
Heartbreak is no joke.
Sounds like Neon had a pretty bad case of it.
She totally did.
It turned out that two of her childhood guy friends were secretly dating.
Huh?
I mean, it's not officially written anywhere, but if you're paying attention, it's super obvious.
Yep.
100% can confirm.
The relationships in Blaze are complicated.
Mirai and Shion Tan are super in love with this dude, Sakuya.
They actually hardcore fight over him.
But Sakuya is totally dating Soma, so those crushes were doomed from the start.
And let's not forget that Neon had it bad for Soma, too.
Oh, yeah, that's crazy.
Kids watch this?
Shion is a genius, by the way.
She's just messed up because she had a rough life.
But that doesn't get her down.
The fact that she's always smiling like she's tricked someone no matter what is what made me love her more than any of the other magical girls.
So, yeah, I have to cosplay her.
But even if you buy the official Black Lily outfit, it's super difficult to alter.
That's why I want you to make a custom one for me that fits perfectly.
My sweet juju is gonna be Black Lily?
I would kill to see that.
As you can tell, Kitagawa loves Shion, too.
She even has her all over her bag.
Well, if you like her so much, then why don't you cosplay her?
Oh, no, I'd rather not do that.
Why not?
I'm way too tall.
Not to mention I'm pretty far off from Shiontan's small and delicate demeanor.
Although I do believe it's okay to ignore all that and just cosplay the characters you love anyway.
But in my case, I love her so much I don't want to destroy her image.
If I'm actually gonna cosplay someone, I'd want to do a good job with it.
Besides, if it's Blaze, I'd totally want to be Neon.
What the hell is happening?
Whatever, you're just stating the obvious!
This sucks so bad.
She's exactly the kind of cosplayer I absolutely love.
I hadn't heard of her before, so it seemed like she was just some idiot who didn't know what cosplaying actually was.
But she does!
She's really not some annoying bitch at all, and I hate that!
I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me!
Why? What'd you do?
Okay, I'm going home.
Right. I'm sure your uniform is dry by now. I'll go grab it.
Wakana Gojo.
Yes?
Give me your contact information. I'll send you more info on Black Lily and my measurements.
Okay, sure.
Don't get all weird about it. It's just so we can talk outfits.
Huh? Get weird about what?
You know, this whole thing. I'm not trying to steal your boyfriend.
What are you talking about? I'm not her boyfriend, and she's not my girlfriend!
I've never had a girlfriend in my entire life!
She's just a friend-friend.
Friend-friend.
So, yeah. I guess I was wrong.
Friend-friend-friend.
Sorry, bro.
Oh, good. Friend-friend-friend-friend.
Oh.
Aw! You don't have a girlfriend, Gojo! That's so sad!
Is she making fun of him?
Maybe she is an annoying bitch after all.
Hold on. Uh, Juju?
Yeah, what?
So, uh...
You know how I said I'd want to cosplay Neon from Blaze instead of Shion
because I'm so tall and kind of loud?
Yeah.
I thought that now might be the perfect time to try it.
Like, fate or something.
So will you cosplay Blaze with...
Hell no!
You shot me down before I finished asking!
What?
Like, put it in the rain.
I like that.
I really love to go away.
We love nosotros.
Yeah, começou così.
Incazura
That's what I've heard
I've heard about it
I don't want to wait for it
I'm going to be in my dreams
Pure pure
The heart that is
Pure pure pure
I can't
My husband
abdomen
I know
Me
You
Don't
Keep
Next time.